A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991, RG 39 FA1505
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991; 39
  - Rockefeller Family, 1987-1991; 26
    - Rockefeller, Mrs. John D., Jr. (Martha Baird) - A-Z (Box 489, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Martha Baird - Personal Assistance Trust, 1965-1985 (Box 491, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, John D. 3rd (Box 489, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, John D. 3rd - Japan (Box 489, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs. John D. 3rd (Blanchette) (Box 489, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, John D. IV and Mrs. Sharon (Box 491, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance (Larry) - A-Z (Box 491, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance (Larry) - Beaverkill Project (Box 491, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance (Larry) - Charitable Lead Trust A-Z (Box 491, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Articles (Box 490, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Automobiles - A-Z (Box 490, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Awards (Box 490, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Awards - Princeton (Box 490, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Birthday - 80th Birthday (Box 490, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Biographical Data (Box 490, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Charitable Trust (Box 490, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Charitable Trust - A-B (Box 490, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Charitable Trust - C-M (Box 492, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Charitable Trust - N-Z (Box 493, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Charitable Trust - Greyston Foundation (Box 494, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Charitable Trust - The Parapsychology Sources of Information Center (Box 494, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Charitable Trust - Savannah Landmark Rehabilitation Project, Inc. (Box 494, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Clippings (Box 494, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Dinners-Luncheons-Reception (Box 494, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Gifts - A-Z (Box 495, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Gifts - Feurestein, George (Box 495, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Gifts - Needleman, Dr. Jacob (Box 495, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Gifts - Oubre, Alondra (Box 496, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Gifts - Rock, Dr. William Pennell (Box 496, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Gifts - Thompson, Keith (Box 496, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Gifts - Richman, Dr. Richard L. (Box 497, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Giving Program (Box 497, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Giving Program 1991 - A-C (Box 497, Folder 3-4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Giving Program 1991 - D-N (Box 498, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Giving Program 1991 - O-Z (Box 499, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Giving Program 1990 - A-B (Box 499, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Giving Program 1990 - C-M (Box 500, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Giving Program 1990 - N-Z (Box 501, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Giving Program 1989 - A-C (Box 501, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Giving Program 1989 - D-Z (Box 502, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Giving Program 1988 - A-D (Box 502, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Giving Program 1988 - E-Z (Box 503, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Giving Program 1987 - A-N (Box 503, Folder 4-5)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Giving Program 1987 - N-Z (Box 504, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Finances (Box 505, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Insurance, 1988-1991 (Box 505, Folder 2-4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Investments (Box 504, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Interviews (Box 504, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Investments - A-Z (Box 506, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Investments - Echelon Systems Corporation (Box 506, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Investments - Jupiter-Zeus Technologies, Inc. (Box 506, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Investments - Messinger Music Company (Box 506, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Investments - Zeno Restaurant, Inc. (Box 507, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Jewelry (Box 507, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Invitations to Speak A-Z (Box 508, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Lincoln School (Box 508, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Portraits (Box 508, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Loans (Box 509, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Loans - Planet Live (Box 509, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Personal - A-Z (Box 509, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Personal - Hearing Aids, 1982-1990 (Box 509, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Planning and Review (Box 509, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - A-Z (Box 508, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Hawaii (Box 508, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - JY Ranch - A-Z (Box 510, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S - Property - JY Ranch - Finances (Box 510, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S - Property - JY Ranch - Legal (Box 510, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S - Property - JY Ranch - Long, Richard (Box 510, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S - Property - JY Ranch - National Park Service, 1978-1991 (Box 510, Folder 6, Box 511, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S - Property - JY Ranch - Visits - General (Box 511, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S - Property - JY Ranch - Visits - Appreciation, 1991 (Box 511, Folder 4-5)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S - Property - JY Ranch - Visits and Appreciation, 1990 (Box 511, Folder 6-7)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S - Property - JY Ranch - Visits and Appreciation, 1989 (Box 512, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S - Property - JY Ranch - Visits, 1988 (Box 512, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S - Property - JY Ranch - Visits, 1987 (Box 512, Folder 4-5)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Massachusetts - Martha's Vineyard - Chasin Sale to LSR (Box 512, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Massachusetts - Martha's Vineyard - Martha's Vineyard Development (Box 513, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - A-Z (Box 513, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - Board of Directors (Box 513, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - Account 2 (Box 514, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - Basement (Water Problem) (Box 514, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - Delorean, John Z. (Box 515, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - Finances (Box 515, Folder 3, Box 516, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - Meetings (Box 516, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - New York City - 620 Park Avenue, 1980-1988 (Box 516, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - New York State - Beaverkill (Box 518, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Pocantico Hills (Box 517, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Pocantico Hills - Outer Lodge (Parcel C-19, C-19A, C-21) (Box 517, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Pocantico Hills - Sale by LSR to DR of Parcels C-3 and C-23 (Box 517, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Pocantico Hills - Lucy R. Waletzky's Pond-Stillman Park (Box 531, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Rockwood Hall (Box 518, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Tarrytown (Box 518, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - St. John (Box 518, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - A-D (Box 518, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - E-Z (Box 519, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Agenda (Box 520, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Articles-Clippings-Printed Matter (Box 520, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Billings Dairy (Box 520, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm (Box 520, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm - Finances (Box 520, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Debevoise, Thomas M. 2nd (Box 520, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Finances (Box 520, Folder 7, Box 521, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - French Property (Box 531, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - The Mansion (Box 521, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Memos (Box 521, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Winks, Robin W. (Box 521, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum (Box 521, Folder 5, Box 522, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum - A-L (Box 521, Folder 6-7)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum - M-Z (Box 522, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum - Cambridge Associates (Box 522, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum - Finances (Box 522, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum - Long Range Plan (Box 522, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum - Monthly Report (Box 523, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum - Printed Matter (Box 523, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Woodstock Foundation - A-Z (Box 523, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Woodstock Foundation - Board of Trustees (Box 523, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Woodstock Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Memorial Foundation (Box 523, Folder 5, Box 524, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Woodstock Foundation - Contributions (Box 524, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Woodstock Foundation - Finances (Box 524, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Woodstock Foundation - Meetings (Box 525, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn (Box 526, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn - A-Z (Box 526, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn - Expansion (Box 526, Folder 4, Box 527, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn - Expansion - Phase I (Box 527, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Resort Corporation - A-Z (Box 527, Folder 3-4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Finances, 1986-1991 (Box 528, Folder 1-2, Box 529, Folder 1-4, Box 530, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Wyoming (Box 530, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - A-Z (Box 530, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Landscaping (Box 530, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Photos (Box 530, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Visits, 1991 (Box 531, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Visits and Appreciation, 1990 (Box 531, Folder 4-5)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Visits, 1989 (Box 531, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Visits, 1988 (Box 531, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Visits, 1987 (Box 531, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Schedules (Box 530, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Purchases (Box 530, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Trips - A-E (Box 530, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Trips - F-Z (Box 532, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Trips - Caribbean (Box 532, Folder 3-4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Trips - Europe (Box 532, Folder 5, Box 533, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Trips - Mexico (Box 533, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Trips - USSR, 1989 (Box 533, Folder 3, Box 534, Folder 1-3, Box 535, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Trusts, 1980-1991 (Box 536, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. - Works of Art - A-Z (Box 535, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs. Laurance S. (Mary French) - Addresses-Remarks-Statements (Box 535, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs, Laurance S. (Mary French) - Awards (Box 535, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs, Laurance S. (Mary French) - A-Z (Box 537, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs, Laurance S. (Mary French) - Dinners-Luncheons (Box 537, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs, Laurance S. (Mary French) - Investments (Box 537, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Michael S. (Box 538, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Mark (Box 538, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - A-Z (Box 537, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Biography (Box 537, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Trust for Children 1976 - Texas Trust, 1976 October 20 (Box 538, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Works of Art - Mexican Collection (Box 538, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Estate (Box 539, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Estate - Attica Litigation (Box 539, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Estate - Monte Sacro (Box 539, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. (Happy) - A-Z (Box 537, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Peter C. (Box 538, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Richard G. and Nancy Anderson (Box 538, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, Rodman C. (Box 537, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, Sandra Ferry (Box 538, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, Steven C. (Box 538, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, Steven C. - Charitable Lead Trusts - A-Z (Box 538, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller, Steven C., Jr. (Box 538, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop (Box 537, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop - Estate - Winrock International (Box 540, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop - Estate - Winrock International - Cousins (Box 548, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop Paul (Box 540, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop - Estate - Winthrop Rockefeller Charitable Trust (Box 540, Folder 4)
    - Simpson, Abby Rockefeller (Box 548, Folder 2)
    - Simpson, Marilyn M. - Charitable Trust - A-Z (Box 541, Folder 1-3)
    - Simpson, William K. (Box 541, Folder 4)
    - Thorn, Laura (Box 548, Folder 3)
    - Waletzky, Lucy R. (Box 548, Folder 4)
    - Weber, Warren and Mrs. Marion R. (Box 548, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1987-1991; 27
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund (Box 541, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - A-E (Box 541, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - F-Z (Box 542, Folder 1-2)
    - Annual Reports, 1987, 1990, 1991 (Box 542, Folder 3)
    - Board of Trustees - A-Z (Box 543, Folder 1)
    - Board of Trustees - A-Z - Cousins (Box 548, Folder 6)
    - By-Laws (Box 543, Folder 2)
    - Campbell, Colin (Box 543, Folder 3)
    - Contributions (Box 543, Folder 4)
    - Contributions - Cousins (Box 548, Folder 7)
    - Ramon Magsaysay Award Foundation (Box 543, Folder 5)
    - Meetings-Minutes, 1991 (Box 543, Folder 6)
    - Meetings-Minutes, 1989-1991 (Box 544, Folder 1-3)
    - Meetings-Minutes, 1987-1989 (Box 545, Folder 1-3)
    - Meetings-Minutes, 1987 (Box 546, Folder 1)
  - David Rockefeller Fund, 1987-1991; 28
    - David Rockefeller Fund (Box 546, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund, 1987-1991; 29
    - Rockefeller Family Fund - A-Z (Box 546, Folder 3)
    - Contributions - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 548, Folder 8)
    - Meetings-Minutes, 1987-1990 (Box 546, Folder 4, Box 547, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller family office (Room 5600), 1987-1991; 30
    - Rockefeller Family Office - A-Z (Box 547, Folder 2-4)
    - 5600, Inc. (Box 548, Folder 9)
    - 5600, Inc. - Meetings-Minutes, 1987-1990 (Box 549, Folder 1-3)
    - Personnel A-Z (Box 539, Folder 4)
      Restricted - Personnel material.
    - Philanthropic Office (Box 548, Folder 10)
    - David Rockefeller - Office Refurbishing, 1986-1988 (Box 539, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller and Company - A-L (Box 550, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller and Company - M-Z (Box 551, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Associates Capital Fund (Box 550, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Discovery Fund (Box 551, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller and Company - 5500 Fund (Box 551, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Finances (Box 552, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Investment Newsletter (Box 552, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 552, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Meetings-Minutes (Box 552, Folder 4, Box 553, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Odyssey Fund (Box 553, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Pioneer Investment Trust (Box 553, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Pioneer II Fund (Box 553, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Pioneer III Fund (Box 553, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Pocantico and Discovery Fund (Box 553, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Rockefeller Balanced Fund (Box 553, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Rockefeller Capital Fund (Box 554, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Family and Associates (Box 554, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Financial Services (Box 554, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Trust Company (Box 554, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Trust Company - Finances (Box 554, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Trust Company - Meetings, 1987-1989 (Box 554, Folder 6, Box 555, Folder 1-2)
    - Venrock - A-Z (Box 556, Folder 1)
    - Venrock - Finances (Box 556, Folder 2)
    - Public Affairs - A-Z (Box 556, Folder 3-4)
    - Public Affairs - Forbes Magazine (Box 557, Folder 1-3)
    - Public Affairs - Greensward Foundation, Inc. (Box 557, Folder 4)
    - Public Affairs - Summary of Media Coverage (Box 558, Folder 1)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - A-M (Box 558, Folder 2-4)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - N-Z (Box 559, Folder 1)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Credo (Box 558, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1987-1991; 31
    - Rockefeller Foundation - A-Z (Box 559, Folder 2-3)
  - Rockefeller University, 1987-1991; 32
    - Rockefeller University - A-Z (Box 560, Folder 1-2)
    - Baltimore, David (Box 560, Folder 3)
    - Contributions (Box 560, Folder 4)
    - Contributions - Cousins (Box 566, Folder 1)
    - Council (Box 561, Folder 1)
    - Fundraising (Box 561, Folder 2)
    - King of Thailand Biomedical Fellowship (Box 561, Folder 3)
    - Printed Matter (Box 561, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center (Box 561, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - Contributions (Box 561, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - Contributions - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 566, Folder 2-3)
  - S, 1987-1991; 33
    - S - Miscellaneous (Box 561, Folder 7)
    - Science - A-B (Box 561, Folder 8-9)
    - Science - C-Z (Box 562, Folder 1-2)
    - Science - A-Z - Cousins (Box 566, Folder 4-6)
    - Science - Center for Science in the Public Interest (Box 562, Folder 3)
    - Science - Center for Science in the Public Interest - Cousins (Box 566, Folder 7)
    - Science - Committee for Responsible Genetics (Box 566, Folder 8)
    - Science - Institute of Noetic Sciences (Box 563, Folder 1-3, Box 564, Box 565, Folder 1)
    - Science - International Student Pugwash, Inc. (Box 566, Folder 9)
    - Science - National Academy of Sciences (Box 565, Folder 2)
    - Science - New Alchemy Institute (Box 567, Folder 1)
    - Science - New York Hall of Science (Box 565, Folder 3)
    - Science - Union of Concerned Scientists (Box 567, Folder 2)
    - Seal Harbor Organizations - A-Z (Box 565, Folder 4)
    - Seal Harbor Organizations - A-Z - Cousins (Box 567, Folder 3)
    - Seal Harbor Organizations - Island Foundation (Box 565, Folder 5)
    - Seal Harbor Organizations - Seal Harbor Fire Department (Box 565, Folder 6)
    - Seal Harbor Organizations - Seal Harbor Fire Department - Cousins (Box 567, Folder 4)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations (Box 568, Folder 1)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Board of Trustees (Box 568, Folder 2)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Contributions (Box 568, Folder 3)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Finances (Box 568, Folder 4)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Fund Raising - A-Z (Box 568, Folder 5)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Fund Raising - Event at the Plaza, 1987 November 2 (Box 568, Folder 6)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Meetings (Box 569, Folder 1)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Meetings - Annual, 1987 (Box 569, Folder 2)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Meetings - Executive Committee, 1987 (Box 569, Folder 3)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Meetings - Program Committee, 1987 (Box 569, Folder 4)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Meetings - Property Committee, 1987 (Box 569, Folder 5-6)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Meetings - Property Committee, 1987 (Box 570, Folder 1)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Montgomery Place (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - T-W, 1987-1991; 34
    - T - Miscellaneous (Box 570, Folder 3)
    - U - Miscellaneous (Box 570, Folder 4)
    - V - Miscellaneous (Box 570, Folder 5)
    - W - Miscellaneous (Box 570, Folder 6)
    - Westchester Organizations - A-Z (Box 582, Folder 5)
  - Welfare, 1987-1991; 35
    - Welfare - A-C (Box 570, Folder 7-8)
    - Welfare - C-Z (Box 571, Folder 1-4)
    - Welfare - A-Z - Cousins (Box 579, Folder 1-6)
    - American Red Cross (Box 571, Folder 5)
    - Center for Community Change (Box 579, Folder 7)
    - Community Service Society of New York (Box 572, Folder 1)
    - The Hope Program (Box 572, Folder 2)
    - Institut Henry-Dunant, Geneva (Box 572, Folder 3)
    - New York City - Department for the Aging (Citymeals-on-Wheels) (Box 572, Folder 4)
    - New York City - Department for the Aging - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 579, Folder 8-9)
    - United Service Organizations, Inc. (USO) (Box 572, Folder 5)
    - United Service Organizations (USO) of Metropolitan New York (Box 573, Folder 1)
    - Visiting Nurse Service of New York (Box 573, Folder 2)
    - Work in America Institute, Inc. (Box 573, Folder 3)
    - Animals - A-Z (Box 573, Folder 4)
    - Animals - A-Z - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 579, Folder 10-11)
    - Animals - Animal Medical Center (Box 573, Folder 5)
    - Animals - Scientists Center for Animal Welfare (Box 574, Folder 1)
    - Animals - Scientists Center for Animal Welfare - Cousins (Box 579, Folder 12)
    - Blind - A-Z (Box 574, Folder 2)
    - Community Centers - A-L (Box 574, Folder 3-4)
    - Community Centers - M-Z (Box 575, Folder 1)
    - Community Centers - A-L - Cousins (Box 579, Folder 13-14)
    - Community Centers - Union Settlement Association (Box 575, Folder 2)
    - Crime Prevention - A-Z (Box 575, Folder 3-5)
    - Crime Prevention - A-E - Cousins (Box 579, Folder 15-16)
    - Crime Prevention - National Victim Center (Box 575, Folder 6, Box 576, Folder 1)
    - Day Nurseries (Box 576, Folder 2)
    - Day Nurseries - Cousins (Box 579, Folder 17)